bestfriendsforfrosting.com 2015-12-12

# Privacy Notice - Best Friends For Frosting

## Privacy Policy

Best Friends For Frosting takes privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat and use the information we collect when you use BestFriendsForFrosting.com or sign-up for our newsletters.

### Notice Regarding Interest-Based Advertising

Partner Websites may allow third-party companies, including ad networks, to serve advertisements, provide other advertising services and/or collect certain information when you visit our website.  Third party companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  Third party may use non- cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this website. These technologies may be used directly on this website. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques. To learn more about this Interest-Based Advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising by those third parties that are members of self-regulatory programs such as the Network Advertising Initiative, please visit the NAI’s website ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)) which will allow you to opt out of Interest-Based Advertising by one, or all, NAI members.

### Personal Information

In order to supply you with Best Friends For Frosting’s weekly emails, we need your email address. Best Friends For Frosting doesn’t collect any information except that expressly provided by you. We will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except as required to provide you with Best Friends For Frosting material. Best Friends For Frosting will never sell, rent, or share your personal information, including your email to any third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent..

### Usage Information

In addition to collecting other personal and non-personal information, Best Friends For Frosting may gather other information on how our site is used. This information is not personally identifiable and will be used to determine how our website is being used. Examples of such information is: How much time do users spend on our site? What pages do they view? What sites did they come from? What sites do they go to? All of this information is collected to help us create a better, faster, more efficient website and provide you with better content.

### Review and Access

Upon request, Best Friends For Frosting will provide you with a summary of the information we’ve collected about you, and the opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

### How to Opt Out

You can unsubscribe from receiving Best Friends For Frosting emails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any Best Friends For Frosting email and following the instructions.

### Third-Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by Glam Media, Burst Media and Google Adsense, our Web advertising partners. View Glam Media’s  privacy policy at

### Tracking

Like most other websites in the universe, Best Friends For Frosting might place or recognize cookies, small text files, on your browser in order to help us retrieve information vital to providing the best possible service. Our cookies allow us to recognize you and simplify your user experience. Best Friends For Frosting will never use cookies to obtain any information from your computer not related to our site.

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

### Links to Other Sites

As a curator of the best possible information, Best Friends For Frosting often links out to other sites. We are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies.

### Security

All of the information described above is recorded restricted database servers.

### Modifications

Best Friends For Frosting may make changes to this policy at any point. If and when we do, we’ll be sure to inform you here so be sure to check back often if you are interested.

### Contact Us

If you have questions about this policy, or about the site, please  **[contact us](http://bestfriendsforfrosting.com/contact/)**  or you could also review our [About page](http://bestfriendsforfrosting.com/about/).
